Introducing the English Nest Nest and the most awaited show ever in the history of the world, this just in.
As today Rita from Italian Pod and Vlovona.
Hello everyone, welcome back to another edition of This Just In.
My name is Marco and I'm here as well with Marco One.
Marco, Marco, which ones which? So they're Marco One and Marco Two, Marco Zero, Marco One.
I thought you were Marco Zero.
I am Naboo and he is Noodles.
I cannot remember Naboo and Noodles.
I like this guest already with taking power.
Just one moment.
You guys haven't had female guests.
I said one moment, one moment.
We want to say hi in the first place to Leo.
We dedicate this episode to the loving memory of Leo.
Yes, exactly.
Where is he?
He is sailing. Let's just say that he...
He's having a samurai adventure.
Yes, I like that. I can't imagine.
So this is a historical This Just In because it's the first time we have a female, or not a, two female guests for the price of one.
Yeah, we didn't like the...
Wait, sorry, she's getting paid?
That's not fair.
I fall for it for four weeks.
Yeah.
Vluvone actually fought very hard.
Very persuasive.
There was this rumor we didn't want any girls inside.
It was totally not.
It's not girls in the clubhouse.
We never said that.
The old bureau is not in its many words.
We never actually said that.
No, no.
It's just rumors that were being spread among the company.
Plus we had like a Gulam and Pete, which are not like sexually, like we are not identifiable.
Yeah, asexual.
Wait, wait, wait. First, first, not girls, just girls.
No pressure.
Rita and Vluvone, let's listen to the profile.
Show's a really interesting history that, you know...
Yeah, exactly.
Now we know who our guests are today.
Who gave you that name, Vluvone?
But do we know who we are?
No.
I want to do the final check on the show, okay?
Okay, okay, okay.
Now...
Nevada, you can ease up on the mic.
You look a little nervous, a little tense.
I mean, I don't even know what Vluvone is.
You have reason to be tense because it's not about girls and boys or blah, blah, blah.
But it's simply that we cannot have more than one guest at a time in this Justine, right?
It's against the law.
But you've always had more than one guest.
No, no, no, no.
It's three hosts.
Okay, so they always a host.
So we have an assistant host and we have one guest today.
No rules have been broken.
There is a way because we know that you both wanted so hard to come in.
So we'll just have a little trivia, a little contest to see which one will be accepted as
the guest of this Justine.
Go with the intro of the trivia.
Okay, so we can start with question number one.
Okay, question number one, Rita and Vluvone.
Vluvone.
Define freedom.
Who goes first?
You.
Freedom is the lack of rules governing a group or an individual person.
Wrong.
Okay, next.
Vluvone.
Freedom is not having what you cannot do.
We still have five seconds.
So you can say something.
All right.
Next.
Next question.
What's the right answer?
Yeah, what's the right answer?
Vluvone.
All right, next question.
Favorite book?
The Brothers Karamazov.
Why?
Because it is an exploration of the human soul and a brilliant portrayal of 19th century Russia
also beautifully written and fantastic characters.
Ron.
Vluvone.
My favorite book is Shopaholic.
Shopaholic.
Why?
Because I like it.
Can we answer the Vluvone later or what?
Yeah, we can answer it later.
What are you doing?
I don't know.
Vluvone.
And you only have three more questions, so we have to see who makes it.
A train leaves from Shanghai South Station on its way to Beijing at 3.15 PM at 200 kilometers
per hour.
Another train leaves Beijing at 3.30 on the way to Shanghai at 230 kilometers per hour.
What are the driver's names?
The question's wrong because trains going to Beijing don't leave from Shanghai South
Station.
They leave from Shanghai North Station.
And the name?
Xiaobe and Xiaoshan.
Xiaobe!
Close, Danny.
Marco1 and Marco2.
Vluvone.
No, no, no.
It was Mr. Wang and Mr. Zhang.
Why?
Because there's the highest percentage of possibility, the most probable name.
For train, for Beijing, from Shanghai.
Don't leave from Shanghai Station.
They leave from Shanghai Station in Xiaobe District.
So we have no right answers up to the moment.
I think you guys are asking bad questions.
It seems like we will not have them next time on This Just Didn.
It's not looking good.
What's the last question?
You do that on purpose.
The last question.
Who is the first emperor of the Ming Dynasty?
Who was the first emperor of the Ming Dynasty?
Qianlong.
Vluvone.
I don't know.
Ah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, it's not looking good.
It seems like...
Zhu Yuanzhang.
That was the right answer.
That was an easy one.
Well, f*** you guys.
This game is stupid.
All right, well, apparently we will not have them as guests next week.
We tried.
We gave you a fair shot.
But we will have a lot of interesting lessons.
Fair smear.
This game was fixed.
But we will have a lot of interesting lessons in English, but I hope.
Yes, we have three interesting lessons coming up next week.
The first one is about thinking to yourself.
What you say when you are nervous or anxious on a date.
Ooh, on a date.
From a man's perspective?
From a man's perspective, of course.
So, am I sweating?
Are my hands sweating?
It is a bit sexy.
It's this English bottle.
It's from a man's perspective.
So, basically, you are checking girl out inside your mind.
No, no, no.
You're on a date with her and you're thinking...
You're nervous.
When should I kiss her?
Should I kiss her now?
Uh-oh, I'm feeling so uncomfortable.
Yeah, yeah.
She touched my hand on purpose.
What is she doing?
All right, the second lesson is going to the dentist.
I hate dentists.
Are we getting a cavity fixed or what?
No, I don't know.
Group canal?
The dentist is a little bit freaky.
I think...
Remember Pete that we had him on the show last week?
Well, he's the dentist in this dialogue, so...
Whoa.
Terrifying.
And our lesson for Friday is we're going to be learning simple math.
So, we're going to be learning about adding, subtracting, multiplying, divide.
Yeah, I could use some of that.
We did a lesson too.
Yes, we did.
You could use a little bit of math.
Two plus two is four.
Eight times eight.
38.
What?
Do you see how fast I am?
64.
64 times four?
173.
You see how fast I am?
Nobody can beat me.
Incredible.
All right, so those are our three lessons coming up next week.
Be sure not to miss them.
And now it's time for...
For user of the week.
User of the week.
All right, so...
Go with the song of the week.
It's...
I don't know.
We don't have time.
We don't have time for the song.
Okay, the user of the week for this week is...
Is Balaganov.
Balaganov.
Nice.
He's from the Balkans.
No.
Sounds like a Slavic name.
He's from Russia.
Close enough.
No, sorry.
Many Russians are Slavic.
Got that one right.
You still don't know the big dynasties for Cyprus.
Yes, yes.
All right, so congratulations.
I guess we can just call him Bala.
Why?
Why Bala did win the user game?
Well, he's actually a new user, and he's been kind of active on the community lately.
And he's got a cool picture.
I think he's windsurfing or something like that.
You can't...
You should stop doing this after giving the user the big title for the picture.
No, it's cool.
It says a lot about their personality.
So anyways, that...
And we also have some interesting news as well.
Next week, Tuesday, April 21st at 10 a.m. Beijing time, we will have a live conference.
Really?
We don't...
I don't know that.
Anyone who wants to join.
We will post a link.
So, are you going to join?
Yeah, you can join.
I can join too.
And is it going to be about something specific, or is it just going to be kind of a free conversation?
We're going to be having...
Emperors of the Ming Dynasty.
We will be teaching about emperors of the Ming Dynasty, and we will be teaching other
things as well, so...
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
Grande saluto, greetings to Liliana, who also tried to enter the competition of joining
as a guest, but didn't qualify.
Yeah, she didn't qualify.
Didn't qualify because of...
Can we say it?
Because of lack of beauty.
I'm sorry.
But Liliana and Rita here...
Are very attractive.
We need to keep a certain status for our show, and of course...
I know it's an audio podcast, so somebody...
She went like, hey, so it's audio.
What does it have to do with my videos?
I said, no, sorry.
It's a company policy.
Yes.
I am sorry.
Yes, exactly.
Next week, we will have JP on the show.
There is a...
Yeah, grande JP.
Grande saluto JP.
We had it already in one, after like...
April Fools, yeah.
April Fools, but we can't wait to have him back.
And I'm going to lead, with my friend Blavona, a women's strike.
We're going to boycott this show because we've been mistreated, Liliana has been mistreated,
and you guys are just mean, mean women haters.
Agree, agree, agree.
I think I'm actually going to go leave the studio now.
Goodbye.
Have a nice week, everyone.
Rita and Blavona, we love you for who you truly are.
Thanks for being here.
Thanks for being.
Thanks for trying out for this Justin.
Unfortunately, he didn't make it, but we will try and have you next time.
All right, guys.
That's all for today.
We'll see you guys next time.
You wish you could have us next time.
If you want to join this Justin, just send an email and you will be entering the contest
too.
Maybe you can be a guest.
Ciao.
All right, bye.
EnglishPod.com.